var questions = 
[
  {
    question: "How do we write an IF statement in JavaScript?",
    answers: ["if i = 5 then", "if i = 5", "if i == 5", "if(i==5)"],
    answer: 4
  },
  
  {
    question: "When can you not trigger JavaScript from an event handler?",
    answers: ["When another event is still being processed", "When JavaScript is disabled", "When the page uses stylesheets", "When it is running locally instead of on the web"],
    answer: 2
  },
  {
    question: "Inside which HTML element do we put the JavaScript",
    answers: ["js tag", "javascript tag", "script tag", "scripting tag"],
    answer: 3
  },
  {
    question: "The 'function' and 'var' are known as",
    answers: ["Keywords", "Declaration statements", "Data types", "Prototypes"],
    answer: 3
  },
  {
    question: "How to insert a comment that has more than one line in JavaScript?",
    answers: ["//This comment has more than one line//", "<--This comment has more than one line-->", "/*This comment has more than one line*/", "*This comment has more than one line*"],
    answer: 3
  },
  {
    question: "How many parameters can be passed in a function?",
    answers: ["none", "as many as you like", "one for each argument", "one"],
    answer: 3
  },
  {
    question: "Which of these is not a valid parameter?",
    answers: ["text", "variable", "an operator", "a number"],
    answer: 3
  },
  {
    question: "You define a method using",
    answers: ["obj.method", "obj.method[]", "obj.method()", "obj-method"],
    answer: 3
  },
  {
    question: "To see if these variables are all equal we would use",
    answers: ["(A == B) && (B == C)", "A = B =C", "(A == B) & (A == C)", "(A = B) && (A = C)"],
    answer: 1
  },
  {
    question: "The code to obtain a random number between 5 and 9 inclusive is",
    answers: ["Math.Floor((Math.random() * 5) + 4)", "Math.Floor((Math.random() * 4) + 4)", "Math.Floor((Math.random() * 4) + 5)", "Math.Floor((Math.random() * 5) + 5)"],
    answer: 4
  },
  {
    question: "Which of these is not a comparison operator?",
    answers: ["<", ">", "!=", "="],
    answer: 4
  },
];